<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Intradocs – Docsy Documentation</title>
    <link>/intradocs/docs/documentation-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docsy Documentation on Intradocs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="/intradocs/docs/documentation-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Docsy example</title>
      <link>/intradocs/docs/documentation-project/goldydocs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intradocs/docs/documentation-project/goldydocs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;pageinfo pageinfo-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a placeholder page that shows you how to use this template site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This section is where the user documentation for your project lives - all the information your users need to understand and successfully use your project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For large documentation sets we recommend adding content under the headings in this section, though if some or all of them don’t apply to your project feel free to remove them or add your own. You can see an example of a smaller Docsy documentation site in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docsy.dev/docs/&#34;&gt;Docsy User Guide&lt;/a&gt;, which lives in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/docsy/tree/master/userguide&#34;&gt;Docsy theme repo&lt;/a&gt; if you&amp;rsquo;d like to copy its docs section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other content such as marketing material, case studies, and community updates should live in the &lt;a href=&#34;/intradocs/about/&#34;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/intradocs/community/&#34;&gt;Community&lt;/a&gt; pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find out how to use the Docsy theme in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docsy.dev/docs/&#34;&gt;Docsy User Guide&lt;/a&gt;. You can learn more about how to organize your documentation (and how we organized this site) in &lt;a href=&#34;https://docsy.dev/docs/best-practices/organizing-content/&#34;&gt;Organizing Your Content&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Docsy</title>
      <link>/intradocs/docs/documentation-project/docsy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intradocs/docs/documentation-project/docsy/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Docsy is a Hugo theme for documentation developed by a Googler and used on many large projects including &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://airflow.apache.org/&#34;&gt;Apache Airflow&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.grpc.io/&#34;&gt;gRPC&lt;/a&gt; to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo websites are static generated, meaning the hosting platform need serve plain HTML/CSS/JS/Blobs files, while a Continuous Delivery pipeline regenerates on Git merges and pushes out updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theme is flexible and  fully customizable, requiring only knowledge of Hugo and basic web development skills. Hugo itself is based on Go lang and directly uses Go&amp;rsquo;s templating language and module system, making it familiar to anyone with Go experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content is authoried in Markdown, with support for tables, and allows for HTML inline. Docsy also packages Hugo Shortcodes which can make more complex functionality available, it&amp;rsquo;s also possible to augment the Markdown renderer with Hooks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site took 1 second to compile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-book-open&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docsy.dev/docs/&#34;&gt;Docsy docs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-code-branch&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/docsy/&#34;&gt;Docsy repo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-code-branch&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/docsy-example&#34;&gt;Docsy Example repo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
